Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE)
Oh. that's beautiful.
It was terrible.
I can't do it.
Hmm. not yet.
But you will.
You're growing up so fast.
You say that all the time.
Yeah. it's because you are.
You look so much
like your sister.
I wish I could remember her.
If I come back and
you're a foot taller...
gonna ground you.
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE)
(HANDLE SQUEAKS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(ARROW WHOOSHES)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(LOUD THUD)
-(MUTED GRUNTS)
(YELLS. GROANS)
(MAN SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY IN GERMAN)
Shh.
(WHISPERS) Remember
what we learned. okay?
Eve. come with me.
Stay quiet.
(MEN SPEAKING GERMAN)
(BLADE SWISHES)
(GROANS)
(BONE CRUNCHING)
-(GROANS)
-(BONE CRUNCHING)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(IN ENGLISH) We opened
our hearts to you.
We embraced you.
We let you. an outsider.
marry a daughter of our clan.
And how did you
repay this kindness?
You took what was
not rightfully yours.
And now. your wife is dead.
to atone for your
transgressions.
Did you think that you
could just walk away?
Hmm?
Where is she?
Where is Eve?
Charming.
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHS)
You're a fucking coward.
You're trying to
convince yourself
that fate absolves
you of your actions.
-There are no choices.
-Yeah.
Does that make what
you do any easier?
It makes what I do...
necessary.
One bullet...
well placed...
can be a magical thing.
It's neither good...
nor evil.
But how a man uses it
reveals his true character.
You wanted choices.
Well. here they are.
You kill yourself.
and your daughter lives.
Or kill me.
and you and your
daughter die together.
Choice is yours.
You've got your choice.
Now. do you have
the balls to do it?
Papa!
(SHOUTS IN GERMAN)
-(GRUNTS)
-(BONE CRUNCHING)
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(KNIFE SWISHES)
-(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(GUNSHOT)
(MUFFLED) Hey.
baby. look at me.
-(SNIFFLES)
-It's okay.
-(MAN SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
-(IN ENGLISH) Come on.
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUNS FIRING)
-(GROANS)
-(EVE GASPS)
Come on.
(GROANING)
Papa.
I'm sorry. honey.
-I never wanted this for you.
-Papa.
I'm sorry.
Papa!
Papa...
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE)
WINSTON: Tchaikovsky.
How lovely.
At a time of loss.
there's nothing easier than pity
and nothing more
difficult than the truth.
as there are no easy
answers for grief.
I'd like to be honest with you.
Would that be all right?
(MUSIC BOX STOPS)
Your father was a good man.
He wanted a free and
open life for you.
Not like the one that
he had to endure.
But we all live with
the decisions we make.
Now he's been taken from you.
I can do nothing about that.
But what I can do...
is offer to take
you to his family.
They will look after you
and. hopefully...
one day become your family. too.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENING)
The Director will see you now.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Does she know who her
parents really were?
Come here. Sit.
You dance. yes?
Mmm-hmm.
I run this theater.
and I am always looking
for new recruits.
I know you.
I know your pain.
What boils inside of
you under the surface.
I can give you somewhere
to put that anger.
Those men took your past.
Don't let them
steal your future.
(DOOR OPENS)
Well?
She says my path is now here
with the Ruska Roma.
(SIGHS)
Very well...
Eve.
Thank you. Mr. Winston.
You are most welcome.
Miss MaCarro.
And know that I will
always be at your service.
(DOOR CLOSES)
My name is Nogi.
Did you know my father?
I did.
Your father was
Ruska Roma. like me.
Like you will be. too.
He was what we call Kikimora.
What is that?
In Slavic mythology.
the Kikimora is a kind of spirit
to those with darkness
in their hearts.
She can be vengeful
and destructive.
Like the boogeyman?
Yes.
But to the innocent...
she can be a protector.
It is...
two sides...
to the one coin.
To kill...
To save.
But. ultimately...
it is up to you to choose.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ROUSING MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(THE DIRECTOR IN RUSSIAN)
(GROANS)
(IN ENGLISH) Are you finished?
(SIGHS) No.
Good.
That will be all for today.
Tend to your wounds
before you get sepsis.
and we have to
cut off your feet.
Tell Tatiana she's next.
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) "Her
Majesty" says you're up.
That woman hates me.
She hates everybody.
TATIANA: Christ. Eve.
Why do you push
yourself like this?
I want to be ready.
Ready for what?
You know what's funny?
When I was a little girl.
I actually did want to
be a real ballerina.
You are a real ballerina.
You're the best dancer here.
That other shit. you'll
learn with training.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
INSTRUCTOR: Fire!
One bullet.
well placed.
can change the world.
The Kikimora's purpose
is to stop that bullet.
INSTRUCTOR: Time's up!
To become Kikimora you
must become the assassin.
You must learn to move like him
and think like him.
For this next exercise.
we will be using
simulated rounds.
What are the rules?
Protect your ward at all costs.
That is the only rule.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
NOGI: Why did you fail?
He's too strong.
NOGI: Do you really believe
that strength has anything to do
with whether you win or lose?
You will always be weaker.
You will always be smaller
and at a disadvantage.
He is beating you
because you are allowing him
to define the terms
of the contest.
You want to win?
Change the terms.
Improvise. adapt. cheat.
Lean into your strengths.
not his.
Fight like a girl.
Begin.
(ELECTRIFYING MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANS)
Good.
(MAN GROANING)
Where is she?
Tatiana's things are gone.
Did something happen to her?
Sit.
Tatiana did not have
the qualities required
to continue with the Ruska Roma.
What are you talking about?
She lacked the killer
instinct I see in you.
Your childhood was taken.
This pain is what drives you.
Tatiana...
there is sadness. not pain.
There's a difference.
You two are now on
different paths.
Then why are you
holding me back?
I'm ready.
Perhaps you are right.
It is time.
This is the final
stage of your training.
(WOMAN GRUNTING)
(CHUCKLING)
Oh. my God.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm a fucking test?
How the mighty have fallen.
Do you know who I am?
No.
I'm you...
in ten fucking years.
(DEVICE CLICKS)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WOMEN MURMURING INDISTINCTLY)
THE DIRECTOR: Somehow
you managed to get out.
but here you are
back where you began.
All of this for what?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(INSTRUCTOR SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY IN DISTANCE)
THE DIRECTOR: With
this. Jardani.
your ticket is torn.
-(SIZZLES)
-(JOHN GRUNTING)
THE DIRECTOR: You can
never come home again.
Take him to the lifeboat.
Do svidanya.
Das vedanya.
EVE: You're him.
The one they call the Baba Yaga.
The students all talk about you.
How do I get outta here?
The front door is unlocked.
No. I mean...
how do I start
doing what you do?
Looks like you already have.
That door will lock
sooner than you think.
You can still leave.
You still have a choice.
Why didn't you leave?
I'm working on it.
NOGI: The Director
feels you are ready
for your first contract.
You will protect this woman.
Katla Park.
Her father is our
primary charge.
He is concerned
that his competitors
may try to get to him by
ransoming his daughter.
Your job is to make sure
they don't get the chance.
To infiltrate past security.
you'll be using a modified
3D printed Glock 43X
with reinforced
carbon fiber barrel.
and polymer rounds.
Rubber bullets?
Problem?
-No.
-You'll find Miss Park
at Minus Eleven.
(ELECTRONIC DANCE
MUSIC PLAYING)
MUSIC CONTINUES)
(LAUGHTER)
(CROWD MURMURS AND CHEERS)
In position.
NOGI: Copy.
I have the principal in sight.
NOGI: Hold your position.
She can dance.
I got movement at ten o'clock.
NOGI: A threat?
Stand by.
Hey! (GRUNTS)
Definitely a threat.
You should get out of the way.
I can't.
I understand.
-(THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING)
-(ALL GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(CROWD SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(BONES SHATTER)
(GRUNTING)
Hey!
(GROANS)
(YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
No. no. no.
I don't want anyone
to touch me right now.
Hey. hey. It's okay.
You're safe now. it's fine.
Let's get you out of here.
(TATTOO MACHINE WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(CAMERA PHONE CLICKS)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(ELECTRONIC ROCK
MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEVATOR DOOR DINGING)
MAN: Hey. what the hell
is goin' on up there?
Somebody respond.
Were you stuck in the elevator?
(ELECTRONIC DANCE
MUSIC PLAYING)
Yes. It was very scary.
(CARS HONK)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(YELPS)
-(BONES SNAP)
-(SCREAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(MAN WHEEZES)
(BLOOD SQUELCHES)
Miss. something's
leaking from your bag.
Yes. Thank you.
No problem.
Is there a reason you've
brought me a severed hand?
Look at the scar.
I've seen this before.
That's the same scar
as the man who
murdered my father.
It was a mark from a tribe.
You knew who they were.
How dare you?
I have been protecting you.
Why didn't you tell
me who they were?
My child. you do not understand.
People with that mark.
they have no rules. no
consequence. no mercy.
They do not interfere
with our business.
and we do not
interfere with theirs.
This is a pact as old as
the Ruska Roma itself.
All these rules. who
are they serving?
When you deal in blood.
there must be rules...
-or nothing survives.
-(GROANS)
Why would a tribe try
to kidnap a child?
I am warning you.
you will not find them.
and hunting for them
will only bring chaos.
I'm ordering you.
do not pursue this.
Do I make myself clear?
(IN RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Please...
take your hand.
(SUSPENSEFUL ROCK
MUSIC PLAYING)
Welcome to the Continental.
Checking in?
No. I'd like to speak
with the manager.
Is he expecting you?
No. he's not.
I see.
And what. may I
ask. is your name?
Eve.
Eve MaCarro.
Let me see what I can do.
(SOFT CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Eve MaCarro of the Ruska Roma.
What a pleasure
to see you again.
Please.
So. what brings you here?
I'm looking for the tribe
that killed my father.
And if I suggested you didn't?
I would smile and nod
and then ignore you.
Ah.
The Director has already
warned me about them
and the rules.
So. I can appreciate
your reluctance.
That's very kind of you.
but a few words of advice.
if I may. Miss MaCarro.
Whatever information you
think these people have.
it might not be in your
best interests to know it.
I still need to know.
"Needing to know" is
what got us banished
from the Garden of Eden.
Are you prepared to be
cast out again. Eve?
Please.
Very well.
I'll give you this. It's
not a tribe. it's a cult.
That kills not
just for business.
but for sport.
While we live among
so-called polite society.
they do not.
Where can I find them?
The precise location is unknown.
But we do monitor them when
they stay at our hotels.
They have access to
the Continentals?
Oh. yes. Better to have them
inside the tent. pissing out.
than outside. pissing in.
And. yes. there is a
man who bears that mark
staying at one of our
hotels at the present...
in Prague. I believe.
On what business?
Shall we?
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello. my dear.
Muriel. be a darling
and bring up the latest
Blackwire submissions
on a Daniel Pine.
Daniel Pine...
Contract submitted
three days ago.
His bounty is set
at two million.
He's currently holed up inside
the Prague Continental...
room 3-1-5.
No outside calls
have been logged.
and he's purchased a
shitload of room service.
Mostly ice cream.
Sweet tooth. hmm?
Hard copy. please.
-(TYPING)
-(WHIRRING)
(WHOOSHES)
CHARON: Sir...
there is a call for you.
From The Director.
(IN SPANISH)
-(COIN CLINKS)
-Checking in.
Certainly.
And how long will you
be staying with us?
Just the night.
Room 314. please.
MAN ON RADIO: Still
no movement from Pine.
What are my orders?
LENA: Keep your eyes on Pine.
We may have a taker.
(DOOR BEEPS)
(WINDOW OPENS)
MAN: You're right.
We have a taker.
A woman. young. dark hair.
She's in.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
Who are you?
Shit.
You're not supposed
to say that word.
Right. Sorry.
-What's your name?
-Ella.
I'm Eve.
You're not here to
hurt my daddy. are you?
Your father?
(SHOTGUN RACKS)
Ella. come here.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Why don't you come stand
behind me. sweetheart?
What do you want?
When I was a child.
men with your mark
murdered my father.
I just want to know
where to find them.
You have no idea what you
just walked into. do you?
No business being conducted.
They're just talking.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(LINE RINGING)
WOMAN: Contract services.
How can I help you?
Account 8-6-5-1.
Name on contract?
Daniel Pine.
Double the contract.
(DINGS)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(PHONE 1 BUZZES)
(PHONE 2 CHIMES)
(PHONE 3 BUZZING)
-(PHONE BUZZES)
-Fuck.
You just made everything
a whole lot worse.
Those people that
you're looking for?
They're surrounding
this hotel right now.
hoping somebody breaks the
rules and takes the bait.
I think they were hoping that
somebody was gonna be you.
(PHONE BUZZES)
Now. you've just made 'em antsy.
Why would they be at the hotel?
They just want me
dead to get to her.
(GUNS FIRING)
Baby. stay down!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SPEAKS GERMAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Ella. come on.
Come on.
He's moving. Hallway.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
Damn it!
Come on.
(FIRE ALARM CHIMING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Back. back. back
the other way. Go!
Wait. wait. Get behind me.
Come on.
(BOTH GRUNT)
PINE: Ella. honey...
let's go.
EVE: Why do they want her?
It's a cult.
No one gets out.
Ever.
You gotta help me
get Ella outta here.
She deserves a better
life than this.
I can't. That's
not why I'm here.
You're Kikimora.
Isn't that what you do?
Help me protect her.
I'll tell you
where to find them.
Please?
ELLA: Daddy...
are we going to die?
PINE: No.
No. baby.
No. not today.
You can trust her.
(CAR HORN BEEPS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
-Hi.
-Huh?
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
EVE: It's okay.
-PINE: Hey.
-How many left?
Two. Maybe ten.
-(LEVEL CROSSING BELL DINGING)
-Oh. fuck it.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
-(TRAIN HORN BLARES)
-(GUNSHOT)
-(SOUND MUFFLES AND DISTORTS)
-Daddy!
(ELLA SCREAMS)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Yes?
LENA: We have the girl.
Good.
Sir. there was
someone else there.
Who?
A woman.
For the contract?
I don't think so.
I think she might
have been after Ella.
Really?
Do we. uh...
Do we know who she is?
Not yet.
I left her for
Continental security.
They started this.
That's bullshit.
I did not break any rules.
-You broke my fuckin' jaw.
-You're still using it.
I didn't kill anyone.
You're going to
need to check out.
Understood.
And what will it
be today. madam?
(COIN CLINKING)
I'd like to go hunting.
Have you ever done
business with these people?
I have not.
(SIGHS)
But you know of them.
You know more than
me. I assure you.
May I be "frank"?
Mmm-hmm.
I prefer to keep it that way.
Hmm.
Are we just window
shopping today.
or would you like
to make a purchase?
Depends on the merchandise.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
After you. madam.
Pardon me.
So...
will this be a large
or small game hunt?
Large.
The V Seven Harbinger TTI.
Thirty rounds of .308.
It's got a Trijicon AccuPoint
1-to-6 optical on top.
and in case you wanna get up
close and make it personal.
you've got a side RMR for
the faster. dirtier stuff.
TTI custom Benelli
M2 21-inch fin grip.
Oversized charging handle.
oversized bolt release.
This will take a
bear's head off.
Easily.
Oh. this is a personal
favorite of mine.
-This...
-(GUNS FIRING)
(YELPS)
Ah! Fuck!
Bastards! Fuck!
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(YELLING)
-(EARS RINGING)
-(SOUNDS MUFFLING)
(MAN YELLS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOTS)
Motherfuckers.
All right...
you didn't hear this from me.
Their precise location
has never been confirmed.
since anyone who's
ever gone looking
has also gone missing.
That's bad math.
However.
whispers suggest they've
been known to gather
somewhere in these peaks.
deep in the mountains
past Abersee and Feldkirk.
It's not much.
It's more than I had.
Thank you.
Sorry about your shop.
I need a car.
(STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Did you think I
would not find out?
That you expressly
disobeyed my orders?
Then tell me who they are.
I told you. we do
not engage with them.
You risk the destruction of
our family. and for what?
Your own selfish reasons.
Return at once or I
will have no choice.
(GASPS)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(WINDING KEY RATTLES)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Can I get you anything?
Just a coffee.
(DOOR OPENS)
(WHISPERS) Come. let's go.
-(DOOR OPENS)
-(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
It's Agnetha!
Send somebody to the restaurant!
Hurry!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GLASS BREAKS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(BONE CRACKS)
-(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(COMMOTION IN DISTANCE)
MAN: Go around the back.
Don't let her escape!
(ALPINE FOLK MUSIC
PLAYING SOFTLY)
I'm not gonna hurt you.
(MUSIC SWELLS)
(SPEAKS GERMAN)
-(BANGING ON DOOR)
-The fuck?
(COCKS RIFLE)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(ALPINE FOLK MUSIC
PLAYING SOFTLY)
(MUSIC SWELLS)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Chancellor. this is The Eye.
What is it?
The outsider has
not been contained.
THE CHANCELLOR:
Engage full protocols.
(BELLS CLANGING ON PA SYSTEM)
(MAN SPEAKING GERMAN)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN: Find her!
Ah.
You're having a
little tea party.
Aren't you going to say
hello to your grandfather?
Where is Daddy?
Is he okay?
You have no idea. Ella.
how worried I was.
All of us.
Your father...
well. he broke our customs.
He was trying to take you away.
Away from me.
Away from your family.
I hate you.
That hate will make
you strong. Ella.
I hate you.
LENA: Chancellor.
We got her.
Is she dead?
She's Ruska Roma.
She has their mark.
(MUFFLED PAINED BREATHING)
You know. I met
your Director once.
It was many years ago in Moscow.
Not a very pleasant lady.
But we did have a respectful
conversation. nonetheless.
A shared understanding of the
roles that we both play...
and. more importantly. the
roles that we don't play.
The Director didn't
send me here.
The Ruska Roma has
nothing to do with this.
Well. it does now.
Why are you here?
If you've come for the girl.
you are gravely mistaken.
Ella is my granddaughter.
Someday. all of
this will be hers.
My son.
well...
he tried to deprive her
of her true heritage.
You put a contract
on your own son?
You may have noticed
we don't take well
to outsiders
meddling in our town.
This is where people like
yourself come to live.
to have real lives.
To raise families.
Would you not like to someday
have a family of your own?
I had a family!
I was a child.
Men came into my house.
Men from your tribe.
Ah.
I see.
This is about vengeance.
They killed my father
and tried to take me.
Tried to take you?
Fate is a very humbling thing.
What is it?
Well. she... she wasn't
working for Pine.
She's here because
I killed her father
when she was a child.
She's your sister.
No.
-(GUNSHOTS)
-For God's sake!
THE CHANCELLOR:
What are you doing?
Lena!
(DOOR CREAKS)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANT HEAVILY)
All this time. I
thought you were dead.
What are you talkin' about?
You don't remember me. do you?
You were born here. Eve.
We both were.
My little sister has come home.
When I was younger.
I used to wonder...
"Why did he take
you and not me?"
I mean. later I realized
it was too late for me.
I'd already taken a life.
But you...
(SCOFFS) He thought
he could raise you
with no memory of this place.
of your true home.
But I guess it never
leaves your blood. does it?
In the end.
we are who we are.
We are not the same.
Your people...
killed my father.
Our father. Yes.
For betraying us.
And then our mother
had to pay the price.
The Chancellor was trying
to save you that night.
He was trying to
bring you back home.
as he would with anyone.
My father was trying to
give me a normal life!
(CHUCKLES)
Well. he would be very proud.
You're forcing children
into this life!
As Ruska Roma has with you.
No!
She gave me a
choice! I chose this!
Oh. did you?
Or did fate just find
another path for you?
At least here we're
honest about who we are.
No Kikimora lies.
We've got eyes on her.
Cabin 83.
She's inside with
Lena. sir. talking.
Take them out.
Sir?
Kill them both.
You heard The
Chancellor. Blow it.
(GROANS)
I was only nine when they
told us you were dead.
Save your breath.
I missed you.
(MAN SPEAKING GERMAN)
MAN 2: (IN ENGLISH)
Everyone. move in.
Check for survivors.
(MEN GROAN)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(YELPS)
(MEN GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
THE CHANCELLOR: Strike team...
Strike team. do you copy?
Is it done?
This isn't done
until you're dead.
(PHONE RINGS)
Yes?
We have a problem. you and I.
And what problem might that be?
That a member of your tribe
has contravened a
centuries old truce.
The Ruska Roma have
no desire for a war.
Especially not with you.
THE CHANCELLOR: Whether
you sent her or not
is of no interest to me.
You will accept
full consequences
of her actions.
Which are?
The end of your tribe.
Your students. your
fucking pets. everything.
Call her off.
THE DIRECTOR: Chancellor.
she's operating
against Ruska Roma.
I could not call
her off if I tried.
Then war it shall be.
Perhaps an agreement
could be struck.
I can send someone
to solve the problem.
Someone capable.
No more bloodshed.
If you agree to this.
you must also agree that
your men will not engage.
If come midnight
she still breathes.
retaliation will be
inevitable and total.
And if the problem
is taken care of?
Then I will reconsider
my response.
THE DIRECTOR: Very well.
I will. of course.
need your location.
A secret I assure
you will die with me.
(SIZZLING)
(GROANING)
Madam. she is family.
THE DIRECTOR: She
has made her choice.
The Baba Yaga.
(MICROPHONE WHINES)
Citizens of Hallstatt...
this order stays in effect
until the bells ring out.
As of now. you do not engage.
Anyone who feels compelled
to go against this order
will be cast out.
Leave the wolf to its prey.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
She sent you here to kill me?
That's up to you.
Or you can leave.
Your choice.
Do you remember me?
From the theater?
Remember what you said to me?
You told me I could leave.
that it was my choice.
It still is.
I'm not leaving.
(SIGHS)
You don't have to do this.
Just leave.
(EVE GROANS)
Leave.
Just... go.
He killed my father.
I know.
Let me finish this.
Midnight.
If it isn't done...
Rules.
And consequences.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
THE EYE: Sir. he's let her
go and she's on the attack.
I recommend we re-engage
full protocols.
(SIGHS)
Attention.
Every citizen is now being
called to hunt the outsider.
(BELL CLANGING ON PA SYSTEM)
MAN: Let's go.
MAN: Let's move it. move it!
MAN 2: Check the boathouse.
MAN 3: You see anything?
(GRUNTING)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(BLOOD SQUELCHING)
-(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(CHOKING)
(GROANS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(YELPS)
MAN 1: She's here!
MAN 2: Hurry up! With me.
Be on alert.
Make sure everything is clear.
(YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(EXHALES)
Cool.
THE EYE ON PA: Attention.
The outsider has
entered the armory.
All teams proceed to the armory.
She wants me...
and she wants Ella.
Orders?
THE CHANCELLOR:
You find her...
and you destroy her.
DEX: Come on.
MAN: Keep your eyes open.
THE EYE: Two men down
at the armory entrance.
I repeat. two men down
MAN: Hold there. Hold.
(MUFFLED
INDISCERNIBLE CHATTER)
Go! Go!
(MAN SCREAMING)
THE EYE: Requesting
all citizens
to the tunnels immediately.
All citizens proceed
to the tunnels.
Move in. I got your six.
Oh. shit.
(MEN SCREAMING)
Over there!
(GUNSHOTS)
(INTENSE ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROUSING ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Go. go!
(MEN SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GROANING)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: She's there!
(GUNS FIRING)
(MEN SHRIEK)
THE EYE: We have lost
sight of the outsider.
All teams be on alert.
Continue to patrol
the perimeter.
MAN: We're on the square.
Eye. report back. Report back.
We're on the square.
THE EYE ON RADIO: Alpha
Team. halt! (BREAKING UP)
(RADIO STATIC)
She has exited the tunnels.
Check behind you.
(MEN SCREAMING)
(DAUNTING ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
-(DOOR OPENS)
-THE EYE: Sir.
In the interest of
Hallstatt's survival.
it would be best
to relocate you.
In 200 years. no
leader of Hallstatt
has ever left the seat of power
to seek shelter.
I understand.
But. sir. we've also
lost track of John Wick.
ELLA: Let go!
Let go of me.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(ROUSING ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING)
(EVE GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
THE EYE ON PA: Attention.
Requesting all citizens...
(MAN SHOUTS IN GERMAN)
(GROANS)
(IN ENGLISH) This is suicide.
It's fucking John Wick.
Come on. He's only one man.
Cut across here.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(SHRIEKS)
-(BRAIN SQUELCHES)
-(ENGINE ROARS)
-(TIRES SCREECH)
Don't you think
we've had enough?
Do you really think you're
going to save her from me?
From...
From all of this?
Whatever happens here...
nothing is going to change.
The village will remain.
the children will be raised.
and the system will
continue as it has
for the last thousand years.
Look at you.
You know that you don't
choose to be a killer.
you are chosen.
Just like your
sister was chosen.
Just like Ella has been chosen.
It is your fate
and you cannot change it.
The only person you're
fighting is yourself...
It's okay.
Let's go.
Hmm?
(LINE RINGING)
THE DIRECTOR: Jardani?
(IN RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) So. she is dead?
He is dead.
Fine.
(TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE
PIANO VERSION PLAYING)
Daddy?
Hey. sweetie.
Come here.
Get up here.
Room 814.
I trust the talk went well?
Checking in. hmm?
Yes.
Safe haven. Miss MaCarro.
You may have cut
the snake's head.
but the body still lives.
They'll be looking for you.
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(SWAN LAKE BY
TCHAIKOVSKY PLAYING)
(PHONE RINGS)
Contract services.
How may I help you?
Name on the account?
Processing.
(PHONE BUZZING)
(FIGHT LIKE A GIRL BY
EVANESCENCE FT. K.FLAY PLAYS)
♪ One step closer
and you're all mine ♪
♪ You leave me no choice ♪
♪ Burned into mind ♪
♪ I'm going in for the kill ♪
♪ There is no other way out ♪
♪ If you need to baby ♪
♪ Cry. cry about it
Why don't you cry? ♪
♪ Time to pay for
what you started ♪
♪ Who's sorry now? ♪
♪ Tell your lies Yeah.
you can run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight
like a girl? ♪
♪ Fight like a girl ♪
♪ And take this world ♪
♪ Tonight. you're the victim ♪
♪ Of your own crime ♪
♪ You made your choice ♪
♪ You'll swallow your fate ♪
♪ Stone cold ♪
♪ Feed the snakes ♪
♪ Hold that fire Say my name ♪
♪ Baby. you can cry ♪
♪ Cry. cry about it ♪
♪ Why don't you cry? ♪
♪ Time to pay for
what you started ♪
♪ Who's sorry now? ♪
♪ Tell your lies ♪
♪ Yeah. you can
run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight
like a girl? ♪
♪ Fight like a girl ♪
♪ Sinner and savior I've
been walking the line ♪
♪ Killers collide ♪
♪ The feeling an
adrenaline high ♪
♪ Violent behavior
in my blood ♪
♪ No one but myself to trust ♪
♪ Vengeance well that
shit's a hell of a drug ♪
♪ Break the cycle
I don't wanna ♪
♪ Break your spinal
yeah I'm gonna ♪
♪ My finger on the trigger ♪
♪ I've been feeding the pain ♪
♪ You'll never
fight like a girl ♪
♪ So I keep winning the game ♪
♪ I wanna see you cry ♪
♪ Cry. cry about it ♪
♪ Why don't you cry? ♪
♪ Time to pay for
what you started ♪
♪ Who's sorry now?
Tell your lies ♪
♪ Yeah. you can
run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight
like a girl? ♪
♪ Sinner and savior I've
been walking the line ♪
♪ Devil disguised ♪
♪ I see it when I
look in your eyes ♪
♪ Yeah. you can
run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight
like a girl? ♪
♪ Fight like a girl ♪
(HAND THAT FEEDS BY HALSEY
AND AMY LEE PLAYING)
♪ I know I should
have the pride ♪
have the spirit ♪
♪ I know you
would tell a lie ♪
♪ If you knew I
couldn't hear it ♪
♪ You'd say it
oh. so proudly ♪
♪ But do you know
your crimes? ♪
♪ And do you think about me? ♪
♪ And were you ever mine? ♪
♪ You say I mean
the world to you ♪
♪ To keep me on my knees ♪
♪ Then dig the
knife in deeper ♪
♪ Just to watch
how much I bleed ♪
♪ I'm stripped to the bone
I don't want to be alone ♪
♪ No matter how I plead ♪
♪ You do it 'cause
you know you can ♪
♪ Turn around and bite
the hand that feeds ♪
♪ Every promise
that you break ♪
♪ Every time you try to
place the blame on me ♪
♪ I don't want to
control the pain ♪
♪ Turn it into
the fire I need ♪
♪ The feeling
rushes through me ♪
♪ Can you still hear me cry? ♪
♪ But after all I'm standing ♪
♪ On my own this time ♪
♪ You say I mean
the world to you ♪
♪ To keep me on my knees
Keep me on my knees ♪
♪ Then dig the
knife in deeper ♪
♪ Just to watch
how much I bleed ♪
♪ I'm stripped to the bone
I don't want to be alone ♪
♪ No matter how I plead ♪
♪ You do it 'cause
you know you can ♪
♪ Turn around and bite
the hand that feeds ♪
♪ I played your twisted game
Played your twisted game ♪
♪ Now watch me walk
through the flames ♪
♪ Choking on the taste
of your mistakes ♪
♪ And now you're the
one on your knees ♪
♪ That's why you bite
the hand that feeds ♪
(GRIPPING ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
TCHAIKOVSKY'S SWAN LAKE)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org